The root of all evil awaits.
The Unspoken is a thriller, horror, mystery film directed by Sheldon Wilson.
In 1997 the close-knit Anderson family vanished from their home without a trace.
No bodies were ever found and no explanation satisfied curiosity.
For 17 years the house has remained undisturbed...until now.
This eerily expert frightener is further enlivened by terrific performances from
‘Suits’/’Arrow’ star Neal McDonough and SILENT HILL/THE TALL MAN/TIDELAND’s Jodelle Ferland.
Angela, played by Jodelle Ferland.
Adrian, played by Sunny Suljic.
Sheriff Bower, played by Neal McDonough.
Deputy Hill, played by Matt Bellefleur.
Sheriff, played by Fulvio Cecere.
Ruby Harris, played by Chilton Crane.
The Unspoken (also known as The Haunting of Briar House) is a 2015 Canadian
horror thriller film written and directed by Sheldon Wilson.
It stars Jodelle Ferland, Neal McDonough, Pascale
Hutton, Sunny Suljic, and Michael Rogers.
The Unspoken premiered at the Film4 FrightFest on October 24, 2015, and was
released theatrically in the United States on October 28, 2016.
The film received generally negative reviews.
The tone is mind_bending and dark and intense.